around the world. In the U.S., we saw 67% growth, where we gained widespread adoption.
We have a leading share now, NBRX share of 47%. 7,000 HCPs now prescribing, and that provides us
a very strong base of physicians, which we can leverage as we move to the early breast cancer
launch. Similarly, outside of the U.S., 35% growth at the preferred CDK4-6 inhibitor. We
have a leading share of 38%. We're the fastest growing CDK4-6 inhibitor in Europe. And when you
look at the early breast cancer setting, we're on track now for a launch in HAP2. We've completed
the manufacturing adjustments in close collaboration with FDA, which we outlined earlier
in the year. We're now anticipating a U.S. approval by the end of quarter three. We remain confident
in a broad label based on the consistency of results that we've seen across the Natalie
population.
And as we announced this morning, we have now updated Natalie data with a median follow-up
of four years. All patients have now completed their three-year course of the medicine. And we
see continued clinically meaningful benefit, consistent safety profile. We believe very
compelling results that will really support the launch of this medicine. And so we're really
excited to present that data at an upcoming medical meeting and continue to support that
Cascalia will hopefully be the preferred medicine for patients.
Now, moving to slide 10. So, Plavicto demonstrated very steady growth versus prior year. Now, when you take a step back on Plavicto, we're now in a transition point where our early rapid uptake is now transitioning to a place where we need to generate demand in the next wave of centers and then eventually out in community oncology, both for the success of Plavicto, but also for the long-term success of RLT. That said, we remain highly confident in the long-term prospects of Plavicto. And we're very excited to be able to have this
study.
to be a multibillion-dollar medicine across the various segments that it will compete in.
We do believe that once we're through this period, we will get back to robust growth,
particularly driven by the PSMA-4 indication and later the HSPC and oligometastatic indications.
We had growth, as I mentioned, of 44% on the quarter.
Now, when you look specifically at the vision population, we estimate our market share is
in the mid-30% with 50% share in established RLT treatment sites.
We see a dynamic where the sites where we're well-established, we could have market shares
above 90%.
We have another group of sites where we're working to go from 50% to 90%.
And then we have about a third of sites of the 475 treatment sites that we're operating
in, where we need to now get from 10% of share of the vision population, hopefully
up over time now to 50%, 90%.
And that's where we're at.
And that will drive the steady growth that we expect over the course of the coming quarters.
Now, when you look specifically at what we're doing to supercharge PluVicto and also enable
us to build a broad capacity for the system to take on RLT, we're increasing our U.S.
promotional efforts, including a field course expansion, which is now completed.
We'll be launching a DTC campaign in quarter three.
We'll also have the phased launch of the patient-ready dose, which is a very important
step.
And then it reduces the time from providing PluVicto from around an hour to less than
10 minutes.
And this will allow sites to hopefully take on more patients, especially sites that have
significant capacity to take on more vision patients.
And then lastly, we have German pricing approved, which is why you've seen the uplift in the
XUS market, XUS sales profile.
So looking ahead, FDA submission for PSMA4 on track in half two.
We already have profiled the positive trend in OS and PSMA4.
China submission is planned in the second half of this year.